Inventory of the Edwin Meese papers, 1941-1991
Hoover Institution Archives
- Presidential Administration of Ronald Reagan File, 1975-1991 (Boxes 554-771, 774)
  - Office of Pardon Attorney, 1986 (Box-folder 770: 19)
  - United States Parole Commission, 1984 (Box-folder 770: 20)
  - Executive Office for the United States Attorneys, 1984 (Box-folder 770: 21)
  - U.S. Marshals Service, 1986 (Box-folder 771: 1)
  - Bureau of Prisons, 1986 (Box-folder 771: 2)
  - Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1985 (Box-folder 771: 3)
  - Community Relations Service, 1984 (Box-folder 771: 4)
  - U.S. National Central Bureau Interpol, 1983 (Box-folder 771: 5)
  - Office of Intelligence Policy and Review, 1986 (Box-folder 771: 6)
  - Justice Management Division, undated (Box-folder 771: 7)
  - Office of Legal Policy, 1985 (Box-folder 771: 8)
  - Office of Public Affairs, 1986 (Box-folder 771: 9)
  - Office of Legal Counsel, 1984 (Box-folder 771: 10)
  - Office of Legislative Affairs, 1986 (Box-folder 771: 11)
  - Office of Liaison Services, 1986 (Box-folder 771: 12)
  - Solicitor General, 1985 (Box-folder 771: 13)
  - Office of Professional Responsibility, 1984 (Box-folder 771: 14)
  - Photographs
    - Meeting with Pope, 1972 July 13 (Box-folder 771: 15)
    - BBQ at Reagan's, 1970 (Box-folder 771: 16)
    - Governor Reagan Welcomes Bob Hope back from United Nations; Gov. Reagan signs U.S. Armor Day Proclamation, 1968, undated (Box-folder 771: 17)
    - California Peace Officers Association conference, 1972 (Box-folder 771: 18)
    - General, 1970 (Box-folder 771: 19)
    - Governor Reagan, undated (Box-folder 771: 20)
    - Family, other, undated (Box-folder 771: 21)
    - Retirement luncheon, 1971 (Box-folder 771: 22)
    - Photo by Honolulu Police Department, undated (Box-folder 771: 23)
    - National Extradition Officials conference, undated (Box-folder 771: 24)
    - General, undated (Box-folder 771: 25)
    - Los Angeles county sheriff, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 771: 26)
    - General, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 771: 27)
    - Governor's orientation, 1969 February 10 (Box-folder 771: 28)
    - Lake Merritt Breakfast Club, other, 1967 (Box-folder 771: 29)
    - Denmark, 1972 (Box-folder 771: 30)
    - Belgium, 1972 (Box-folder 771: 31)
    - General, undated (Box-folder 771: 32)
    - General, undated (Box-folder 771: 33)
    - Fortieth Aviation Company, 1969 (Box-folder 771: 34)
    - General, 1972 (Box-folder 771: 35)
    - Colonel Palumbo, 1973 (Box-folder 771: 36)
    - General, undated (Box-folder 771: 37)
    - General, 1970 (Box-folder 771: 38)
    - Rome, undated (Box-folder 771: 39)
  - Plans for a Ronald Reagan Library at Stanford University (oversize), undated (Box 772)
  - See: Gubernatorial Administration of Ronald Reagan File (Boxes 772-773)
  - Meeting materials, 1985 May-November (Box-folder 774: 1)
  - Attorney General recusal, 1985 May 24, 1987 April 8 (Box-folder 774: 2)
  - Attorney General schedules, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 774: 3)
  - Independent Counsel: DOJ test, 1987 April 24 (Box-folder 774: 4)
  - Independent Counsel: Litigation, 1987 February 25 (Box-folder 774: 5)
  - Independent Counsel: Legislative revisions, undated (Box-folder 774: 6)
  - Independent Counsel: Morrison filings, 1987 March 17 (Box-folder 774: 7)
  - JNR - Independent Counsel, 1986 (Box-folder 774: 8)
  - Mexico: Cortez case, 1986 August 15 (Box-folder 774: 9)
  - Mexico trip, 1986 September (Box-folder 774: 10)
  - Mexico trip (October 8-10, 1986) (Box-folder 774: 11)
  - Representation fund, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 774: 12)
- Declassified U.S. Government Records, 1967, 1986-1988 (Box 770)
  Formerly security-classified records of the U.S. government, released in full or in part. Includes some interfiled, unclassified government records. Arranged chronologically by date of release by Hoover, thereunder by date of creation.
  Most of the declassified records from this collection were returned to their original folders; in these instances, there is a note in the finding aid indicating the presence of these materials.
  - 2013 May release of declassified records, 1986 October-November (Box-folder 770: 22)
    Photocopies of handwritten notes from meetings with various individuals, including George Shultz, Bill Casey, Sam Nunn, and Ross Perot.
  - 2016 March release of declassified records, 1967, 1988, undated (Box-folder 770: 23)
    Letter to the President [Lyndon B. Johnson] from the National Advisory Commission on Civil Disorders, 7 October 1967 (originally in Box 178); resolution and talking points regarding human rights in Cuba, undated (originally in Box 628); and National Security Briefing summary, 21 July 1988 (originally in Box 635).
  - 2018 release of declassified records, 1985-1988 (Reading room workstation)